MÁTRA SENNA

Full-Stack Web Developer



🔾 Vitória - ES - Brazil 🛮 🖭 EU Passport

↓ +55 27 99248 4208

■ mairasenna@gmail.com

in mairasenna 🌎 msma87 🔗 Portifolio

Profile

I'm one of those people who loves tackling problems head-on and isn't afraid to take the lead. Ever since I was young, I've shown leadership skills in both sports and the classroom, and my adventurous spirit led me to unforgettable international experiences.

Although I graduated in Business Administration, I discovered my true passion in the IT field. After exploring various professional roles, I realized that web development allows me to combine my passion with my skill set and professional background to achieve outstanding results.

I'm super excited about this new chapter and can't wait to give my best to the teams and companies I'll be working with!

Skills

Languages — English (fluent) | Portuguese (native) | Spanish (beginner)

Project Management — Agile | ITIL | Scrum | Process improvement

Soft Skills — Communication | Colaboration | Leadership | Multitasking

Technical Skills — CSS | Copilot | Figma | Git | GitHub | Heroku | HTML | JavaScript | OpenAl | Ruby | Ruby on Rails | SQL | Terminal

Technical Projects

GigGoers 🛮 12/2024

- Development of a mobile app for discovering concerts and festivals in São Paulo, completed within two weeks with a four-person team.
- Demo (in Portuguese) 🛮

ChefToi 🗷

11/2024

- Development of an online marketplace connecting personal chefs with clients, delivered in one week through strong teamwork and problem-solving.

Cronos Concursos

10/2024

- Enhancement of the visual identity for an educational platform, improving user engagement.

Professional Experience

BITKA Analytics

Scrum Master

09/2022 - 06/2024 | Vitória - ES, Brazil

- Directed Agile teams for IT projects.
- Led backlog management, stakeholder communication, and Scrum ceremonies to ensure on-time delivery.

Business Analyst

12/2020 - 08/2022 | Vitória - ES, Brazil

- Facilitated communication between business stakeholders and technical teams.
- Translated complex requirements into actionable solutions, improving delivery efficiency.

Marriott International

Front Office Associate

08/2019 – 11/2020 | London, United Kingdom

- Strengthened customer satisfaction by effectively resolving high-stakes guest issues while coordinating operational processes to ensure seamless service delivery.

Q Apartments

Global Guest Relations Executive

11/2018 - 08/2019 | London, United Kingdom

- Elevated service quality by implementing customer-focused solutions and managing reservations.

Gapso Analytics

IT Analyst – ITIL Office

10/2014 - 02/2018 | Vila Velha - ES, Brazil

- Managed and optimized Asset Management processes for operational efficiency.
- Streamlined workflows through process automation nd coordinated with clients and suppliers to resolve issues and align expectations.

International Corp

Foreign Trade Analyst

02/2012 - 06/2014 | Vitória - ES, Brazil

- Managed customs clearance and logistics for international trade operations, ensuring compliance and cost optimization.

SLE

IT Analyst III

12/2010 - 12/2011 | Vitória - ES, Brazil

- Supported on-site international project, coordinating teams and providing user training to ensure alignment and timely delivery.

Administrative Assistant

01/2010 - 12/2010 | Vitória - ES, Brazil

- Supported executives with travel logistics, budget management, and document preparation.

Education

Full-Stack Web Development

Le Wagon 🛮

10/2024 - 12/2024 | São Paulo, Brazil

- 9-week full-time intensive bootcamp
- Construction of two projects showcasing technical and teamwork skills.

MBA in Financial Management, Auditing, and Controlling

MMurad - Fundação Getúlio Vargas

2014 - 2016 | Vitória, Brazil

Bachelor's in Business Administration

UNIVIX

2005 - 2009 | Vitória, Brazil

Graduated with Honors.



- ITIL Foundation V3